树 屋
字 幕 组
郑重声明:本作品之片源、字幕均来自互联网，版权归原电影公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，否则一切后果由该组织或个人承担！本字幕组和制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
听写 汪馒头 wangyj 蔺殊白 mml
翻译 陌初熏 谢尔曼 许文文
校对 Doggy 阿尔贝
时间轴 墨君羽 呵呵哒 耀耀 许文文
特效 阿贝3104
压制 小新
总监 烟火
美味汉堡
Welcome to Good Burger, home of the Good Burger!
欢迎光临美味汉堡 美味汉堡之家
Can I take your order?
你需要点什么
Just a Good Burger please, and I'd like that to go.
只要一个美味汉堡 打包带走
One Good Burger.
一个美味汉堡
Ed!
艾德
I see you!
我能看到你
Don't sell me yet, please!
不要卖了我 拜托
I wanna stay here with you!
我想和你留在这
We love you, Ed!
我们爱你 艾德
Come with us, Ed!
和我们一起吧 艾德
Fly, Ed. Fly!
飞起来 艾德 飞起来
I'm flying with fast food!
我和汉堡们飞起来了
Whoa! Flying with hamburgers!
哇哦 和汉堡一起飞
Welcome to Good Burger, home of the Good Burger.
欢迎光临美味汉堡 美味汉堡之家
Can I take...
我能
A clock!
闹铃
I'm a dude,
我是个花花公子伙计
He's a dude,
他是个伙计
She's a dude,
她是个伙计辣妞
'Cause we're all dudes, hey!
我们都是伙计 嘿
I'm a dude,
我是个伙计花花公子
He's a dude,
他是个伙计
She's a dude,
她是个伙计辣妞
Hey, hey, Alfalfa!
嘿 嘿 阿尔法尔法
Would you please take my order?
能让我点单了吗
Whew! Sorry, no can do!
抱歉 我不能
I'm the drive-through guy.
我是跑堂的
You need the counter guy.
你需要的是前台的伙计
Hey, where's Ed?
嘿 艾德人呢
Whoa whoa whoa whoa, wait wait wait...
哇哦 等等
Yeah!
耶
Morning girls!
早上好 女孩们
I'm sorry!
对不起
I'm sorry! Hang on!
对不起 撑住
I'm gonna get to it!
我来解开
Sorry!
抱歉了
My bad!
我的错
Miss! Miss!
女士 女士
Could I please order some food?
能让我点些吃的吗
Oh no problem!
没问题啊
Okay uh...
好的 额
Let me get some...
我要来点
Ed!
艾德
Ed?
Watch out, lady!
小心 女士
Watch out! Watch out!
小心 小心
Hey!
嘿
Hey baby!
我的孩子
My baby!
Watch out! Baby coming through!
小心 宝宝来了
Put it up man, put it up!
投篮 伙计 投进去
Yeah!
耶
Huh?
额
That's it.
到此为止了
That's it. Five more seconds, I'm calling manager!
到此为止 再过5秒 我要打电话给你们的经理
You think I'm kidding?
你觉得我是在开玩笑吗
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
Welcome to Good Burger, home of the Good Burger.
欢迎来到美味汉堡 美味汉堡之家
Can I take your order?
你需要点什么
Well, it's about time.
好吧 来的是时候
Can I get two Good Burgers?
能给我来两个美味汉堡吗
Aw, sorry dude. I have to go get them.
对不起 哥们 我得去取
Customers aren't allowed in back.
客人不允许到后台的
Just get me two Good Burgers!
快给我两个美味汉堡
Dude, I just can't give you two Good Burgers.
兄弟 我不能只给你两个美味汉堡
You have to pay for 'em!
你得付款
Forget it!
算了
I've had it up to here with Good Burger.
我受够美味汉堡了
I can't wait for Mondo Burger to open.
我迫不及待的等蒙多汉堡开张了
Mondo Burger?
蒙多汉堡
What's Mondo Burger?
什么是蒙多汉堡
Ed.
艾德
Do you see that giant building there across the street?
你看到街对面那幢大楼了吗
The one that they've been building for ten months?
那栋他们已经造了10个月了的
Oh I see it.
哦 我看到了
That's Mondo Burger, Ed.
那就是蒙多汉堡 艾德
And they'll open in like three days.
他们在三天后开张
Cool!
酷
It's not cool, Ed.
一点都不酷 艾德
They are competition.
他们是竞争对手
Big competition.
很大的竞争对手
Yep.
好吧
- They could put us out of business.   - That's right. What are we gonna do next?
-他们能让我们失业   -是啊 那我们接下去做什么呢
Alright, now. Come on!
行了 现在 振作起来
Good Burger has been here for over 40 years.
美味汉堡已经有40多年历史了
People love us!
大家喜爱我们
Most of us.
我们中的大多数人
And nobody is putting Good Burger out of  business!
没人可以让美味汉堡关门
Yeah!
是的
Nobody!
没人
Yeah!
是的
*布瑞德戴尔中学
Alright, people.
好了 同学们
Two more minutes before the end of the test.
再过两分钟期末测验结束
I know what you're thinking, my brother.
我知道你们在想 兄弟
Why?
为什么
Why would this man give us a test
为什么这个男人要让我们做测验
on the last day of school before summer start?
在暑假即将开始的最后一天
Well I'ma tell you why.
好吧 我来告诉你们为什么
Because-
因为
the mind never sleeps.
思想从不睡觉
Can I get a witness?
来个证人行吗
Hallelujah...
哈利路亚
Outta here!
离开这里
Summer vacation...
暑假
Summer vacation!
What's the hurry, my brother?
这么急干什么 兄弟
Uh... My hurry is that it's now officially summer vacation, and yet,
额 我急是因为暑假正式开始了 然后
I'm still looking at you.
我还是在看着你
You know... you're an amazing student.
你知道的 你是个很棒的学生
I mean, you sit there and you get your test done first and...
我是说 你坐那第一个把测验先完成 然后
And you were concentrating so hard,
你如此专注
I thought you were asleep.
我以为你在睡觉
Next time, make it more challenging!
下次让考试更有挑战性点
That's what I want to talk you about.
那就是我想对你说的
Challenges, potential, using your mind.
挑战 潜力 思考一下
'Cause I'm worried about you.
我担心你
I'm worried about you too.
我也担心你
Have you seen yourself lately?
你最近有注意到你自己吗
The fro, the boots, and this jacket!
这发型 靴子和夹克
You have a nice summer, Shaft!
你很夏天啊
Hey,  wait up!
嘿 等等
So uh... how do you think you did on the exam?
额 你考试考得怎么样
Sir! Summer vacation started 48 seconds ago.
先生 暑假刚刚48秒前开始
That means that school, work, or anything in that nature now
意味着学校 作业 或者任何相关的东西
is officially off limits for the next three months.
在接下来的三个月里可以不用理会了
Nice car.
很酷的车
This yours?
你的吗
No, it's my mom's,
不是 我妈妈的
and she's away on business in New York!
她在纽约出差
And she lets you drive this while she's out of town?
她不在这里的时候让你开车吗
Nope.
没有
Ed! Ed
艾德 艾德
Expect you to move!
你能挪一下吗
Ed!
艾德
Ed! We have a delivery.
艾德 我们有个外卖单
But I don't do deliveries.
但是我不负责外卖啊
You do for the time being.
现在起你负责
I fired O'Malley.
我把奥马利炒鱿鱼了
How come?
为什么
Because the boy showed up the work without his pants.
因为他没穿裤子就来上班
Now please! Make this delivery.
现在请你送外卖去
The address is on the back.
地址写在后面
It shall be delivered.
这即将外送到达
So what's your plan for the summer?
这个夏天你有什么计划
Let me tell you boy.
让我来告诉你
I plan to wake up every day at around noon.
我打算每天睡到中午醒
Then I'm a lay up at a pool, order some Chinese food,
然后泳池边躺躺 点点中国菜
maybe invite some fine females over to share an egg roll or two.
或者邀请一些女性朋友来分享下蛋卷
Then I'm gonna wake up the next day,
然后第二天醒来
do it all over again.
重复一样的事情
Know what I'm saying?
知道我在说什么吗
Yeah. Man you're lucky.
知道 你太幸福啦
My folks are making me get a summer job.
我家人强迫我做暑期工呢
See, that's it right there.
瞧 你拥有这个权利
You gotta explain things to parents.
你得跟你的父母解释
Like summer vacation.
比如暑假
The keyword there is va-ca-tion.
关键词是假期
See what I'm saying?
明白我说的了吗
... She's a dude,
她是个伙计
We're all dudes, hey!
我们都是伙计 嘿
I'm a dude,
我是个伙计
He's a dude...
他是个伙计
... She's a dude, hey,
她是个伙计 嘿
'Cause we're all dudes, hey!
因为我们都是伙计 嘿
I'm a dude...
我是个伙计
Get off the...
走开
My afro!
我的发型
Why?
为什么
Oh. Brother Reed.
哦 瑞德 老兄
You have messed up my afro.
你毁了我的发型
I...
我
Don't worry, bro.
不要担心 兄弟
Now just be cool.
冷静下
Let me handle it.
我来处理
Alright, Jake?
好吧 杰克
Jake?
杰克
Jake!
Oh no.
哦 不
Oh baby...
哦 我的宝贝
Oh! Oh no!
哦 不
Oh my grill!
哦 我的挡板
Oh! My dude.
哦 我的老天
Oh!
哦
See, when I left school today, I didn't think I was gonna run into you this summer.
当我今天离开学校的时候 我就没想过会在这个夏天撞见你
I didn't think you were gonna run into me!
我没想到你会朝我撞过来
I mean, just run into me like this.
我是说 以这样撞的方式
You're in trouble with me, young man.
你惹上麻烦了 年轻人
- You're in trouble with me!   - No, listen!
- 你惹上麻烦了   - 不 听着
Mr. Wheat, listen!
惠特先生 听我说
It wasn't my fault.
这不是我的错
See, there's a nut on some roller blades.
有一个笨蛋踩着滑轮
He skated into my vision sight,
他突然滑入我的视线
and I couldn't have seen that so I swerved...   - Rollerblades?
我没注意到 只能转方向   - 滑轮鞋
Rollerblades?
滑轮鞋
- He was spinning around like that,   - I don't wanna hear!
- 他像那样急转身   - 我不想听
- and then I couldn't control...   - I don't wanna hear!
- 我没办法控制   - 我不想听
Know how much that car cost me?
你知道这车花了我多少钱吗
No.
不知道
Do you know?
知道吗
No.
不知道
That's a $22,000 car.
22,000美元的车
22,000 dollars!
22,000美元
And that's just the base price.
而且只是基础价
Not include the chrome.
这还不包括镀铬
See?
看见没
I waited four weeks for the chrome
我等了4个多星期就为了镀铬
You can't get four wheels for a base price.
你个基础价买不到这四个轮子
See that leather?
看到皮革了吗
That's Detroit leather.
那是底特律皮革
You got to order Detroit leather from Detroit!
你得从底特律定底特律皮革
What's that tell you?
这些告诉你什么
They always get you with them extras.
他们老是给你加价
Give me your driver's license.
把你的驾照给我
Give me your driver's license
Regarding my driver's license...
关于我的驾照...
I'll give it to you, but you're gonna have to wait.
我会给你的 但是你得先等等
For what?
为什么
About a year?
大概一年
Oh no.
哦 不
That's when I get one.
当我拿到的时候
No. No.
不 不
When they put it in my hand.
当他们给我的时候
- You don't have a driver's license.   - No.
-你没有驾照   -没有
I know you don't have no insurance, do you?
我知道你没有保险 对吗
I guess... I hate to do this, young man.
我觉得我讨厌这么做 年轻人
I hate to put a black man in jail.
我讨厌送黑人进监狱
But I have to call the police.
但是我不得不报警
- Black man in jail?   - I hate to do this.
-黑人进监狱   -我不想这么做
You ain't got to. I'm just a kid!
你不能 我还只是个孩子
No no no!
不 不 不
Don't call the police!
不要报警
Don't call the police.
-No please! Don't call the police.   - Out of my way.
- 不要拜托 不要报警  - 让开
I can't let them find out I was driving without a license, sir!
不能让他们知道我无证驾驶 先生
Please!
拜托啦
Let me fix it!
让我来处理好
Let me fix it! Let me fix it!
让我来处理 让我来处理
Alright.
好吧
Alright?
Yeah, alright.
是的 好的
Yeah. Yeah, I'll let you fix the car.
好的 我会让你修车
So uh... how much do you think is gonna cost to fix?
额 你觉得修好的话要多少钱呢
1900 dollars?
1900美元
I don't have 1900 dollars!
我没有1900美元
That's alright. Maybe your parents will help you out.
那好吧 或者你的父母可以帮你
I'll just give them a call.
我打电话给他们
Wait. I'll get the money.
等等 我会筹到钱的
No you can't get the money.
不 你不可能筹到钱
I know you got the summer. You just wanna be free.
我知道你开始暑假了 你只想要自由
- We'll just call you parents.   - No, wait wait wait wait.
-还是打电话给你父母吧   -不 等等 等等 等等
I will...
我会
I'll...
Ow...
啊哦
I'll...
我会
I'll get a summer job.
我会找份暑期工
Bun!
面包
Patty!
牛肉饼
Topping!
配料
Sauce!
酱汁
Assemble!
组合
Bun!
面包
Patty!
牛肉饼
Topping!
配料
Sauce!
酱汁
Assemble!
组合
Bun!
面包
Patty!
牛肉饼
Topping!
配料
Sauce!
酱汁
Assemble...
组合
Come on little bun...
拜托 小面包
Beef patty...
牛肉饼
Yeah.
对
Okay, yeah.
对 这样
Oh that's nasty...
哦 太恶心了
Alright.
好吧
Yo, my man, can I borrow some lettuce?
哟 朋友 能借我点生菜吗
Huh? Can I borrow some le...
我能借点
You.
你
Who?
谁
You!
你
Look at this mess.
看看这团糟的
I can explain.
我能解释
See, I was trying to put the big old beef patty...
你看 我在尝试放块大的老的牛肉饼...
on the bottom half of the bun,
在半块面包的底部
you know, before the...
你知道的 在那啥上面
the tomato gets all slippery...
番茄变得很滑
Oh that's slippery...
哦 很滑
Oh. I'm sorry.
哦 对不起
And then, you know the pickle bits was making me do the wrong
然后 你知道的酸黄瓜让我弄错了
because they're flexible.
因为它们很灵活
They're not crunchy.
而不是脆的
And...
然后...
Yo man, back me up on this
哟 伙计 帮帮我吧
Oh again with the whistle.
哦 又吹哨子
Shut up.
闭嘴
Just be quiet.
安静点
Well it'd be a lot more quiet if you stop blowing the whistle.
如果你不吹哨子的话会很安静
Watch your mouth, you pestiferous little maggot.
注意你说的话 邪恶的蛆虫
Now, I'm familiar with the term maggot, but...
现在 我清楚了蛆虫这个词 但是
pestiferous?
邪恶的
Burn this into the front row of your brain, chuckles.
让你的大脑牢牢记住这句话 小鸡仔
here's one thing Kurt cannot stand.
科特不能忍受的
It is an incompetent bumbling sloppy fast food employee.
就是无能的笨拙的懒散的快餐雇员
Yum.
美味
Yeah.
好
Ed!
艾德
What are you doing inside the milk shake machine?
你在奶昔搅拌器里干嘛
Trying to fix it.
试着修理它
Did you turn on the switch?
你开关开了吗
No
没有
Strawberry Jacuzzi!
草莓浴
People.
同志们
I'm fully stoked about being in charge of every single one of you.
我很荣幸来管理你们每一位
Within two years, Mondo Burger is going to the biggest
在两年内 蒙多汉堡将要成为这个星球上
burger chain on this planet.
最大的汉堡连锁店
Oh yeah.
对了
First we gotta beat out our big competition across the street,
首先我们要打败街对面的有力竞争对手
Good Burger.
美味汉堡
From now on, your life is Mondo Burger.
从现在开始 蒙多汉堡就是你们的生命
You can forget about your friends.
你们可以抛开你们的朋友
You can forget about your family.
抛开你们的家人
Because Kurt
因为科特
is now both your mother and your father.
现在是你们的母亲和父亲
Kurt must like awfully strange naked.
科特裸着的时候一定很古怪
Who said that?
谁说的
Who talked while Kurt was talking?
当科特在说话的时候 谁在说话
It was him.
是他
He uttered something.
他说了些什么
Why, I should have known.
为什么 我早该知道了
I'm sorry I uttered.
对不起 我说话了
You think you're funny, don't you, bro?
你自以为很幽默 是吗 兄弟
You know what?
你知道吗
At Mondo Burger, there are no comedians.
在蒙多汉堡 没有喜剧演员
You mess with Kurt, and you go into the grinder.
你惹毛了科特 你就会被粉碎
Okay. Now this grinder of yours,
好吧 你说的粉碎机
is it a real grinder or is that some kind of a metaphor?
这个粉碎机是真的还是一个比喻
That's it.
够了
You're gone.
你被解雇了
Adios, TKO, historical.
再见 完败 历史
Wait, wait, wait!
等等 等等 等等
I won't be funny no more. See?
我不会再搞笑了
Security.
保安
You ain't gotta bring the men down here.
你不要叫这些人过来
Wait a second.
等一下
Kurt, come on. Please!
科特 拜托 拜托了
I need this job!
我需要这份工作
Take out the trash!
把这个垃圾扔出去
Trash?
垃圾
Oh now, look at here...
哦 现在
Get this loser out of my face.
把这个失败者带出去
Loser?
失败者
- Oh now you're about to push me a little too far.   - You want a piece of me?
-现在你惹火我了   -你想要撕碎我揍我
Yeah! Extra crispy, please!
是啊 狠狠的
Oh see, you're lucky you brought your friends down here.
瞧 你很幸运叫了人过来
Is this really necessary?
真的有必要吗
Kurt, please! I need this job!
科特 拜托 我需要这份工作
Please! I need this job!
拜托 我需要在这份工作
Excuse me.
请问
Look. I order one Good Burger with nothing on it.
我点了美味汉堡不要放任何其他东西
That's what I gave you.
那就是我给你的
No. You gave me a bun.
不 你给了我个面包
Just a bun.
只是个面包
Look, there's no meath in here.
你瞧 里面没有肉
But you said you wanted nothing on it.
但是你说了什么都不要放
Yes, well, I expected a meat patty.
是的 但是除了肉饼
Dude, a meat patty is something.
兄弟 肉饼是东西
You said nothing.
你说什么都不要
Fizz, is a meat patty something or nothing?
费兹 肉饼到底是不是个东西
Uh... Something?
额 是个东西
I win.
我赢了
Alright. That rips it.
好了
I am reporting your name to the manager!
我要向你的经理投诉
The manager already knows my name.
经理知道我叫什么
I'll see you in the hell.
地狱见
Okay. See you there!
好啊 那儿见
Such a nice guy.
真是个不错的人
I don't know why he had to throw the bread everywhere.
我真搞不明白他为什么乱扔面包
Jeez.Jeez
One more Good Shake.
再一杯饮料
Good, good. Keep 'em coming.
好的 好的 再来点
Dude, don't you think you've had enough?
老兄 你不觉得你已经喝的够多了
Hey. You look familiar.
嘿 你看起来很脸熟
Don't I know you from somewhere?
我们在哪里见过吗
Ever been to Australia?
你去过澳大利亚吗
No.
没有
Me neither.
我也没有
Couldn't sworn I've seen you at someplace before.
我发誓我之前在哪里见过你
Hey, I know!
嘿 我知道了
Maybe I'm someone famous.
或许我很出名
You know, like a baseball player?
你知道的 像篮球球星
Or a pretty nurse.
或者美丽的护士
What?
什么
Man, what in the world are you talking about?
先生 你在说些什么
Okay, okay. I give up.
好了好了 我放弃了
Who am I?
我是谁
I don't know who you are,
我不知道你是谁
or where I know you from,
或者你是哪人
or why you think you're an attractive nurse.
或者为什么你觉得你是有魅力的护士
But I'm sure I don't wanna know you any longer.
但是我确信我不想更多的了解你
Now please go away.
现在请走开
I've had a very bad day.
我今天过的非常糟糕
What's wrong?
怎么了
Were you bitten by a sheep?
你被羊咬了吗
What?
什么
Did you lose your trousers?
你丢了裤子吗
No!
没有
Look. You're an unusually bad guesser,
瞧 你真是完全不会猜
so I'm going ahead and tell you why I'm upset.
所以我会告诉你我为什么不开心
I gotta come up with $1900 to fix some jerk's car,
我需要1900美元去修理某个混蛋的车
another $800 to fix my mother's car
另外800美元修理我妈妈的车
and I just got fired.
而我刚刚被炒鱿鱼
Man. Can't believe Kurt fired me from Mondo Burger.
天啊 不敢相信科特把我从蒙多汉堡踢了出来
I mean, he yelled at me.
我是说 他冲我大吼
Then he insulted me.
侮辱了我
He made fun of me.
还取笑我
Boy! You must really suck!
伙计 你肯定是烂透了
See, right about now, I'd slap you in your head,
此时此刻 我想扇你脑袋
but I'm not quite sure that
但是我不是很确信
your brain would understand the concept of pain.
你的脑袋是否能感知到疼痛
Hey!
嘿
Wanna see my belly button?
想要看我的肚脐吗
Well.
好吧
It was very unusual to meet you...
遇见你真是不同寻常
Ed.
艾德
I'm gonna go now and try to beg someone for a summer job, man.
我现在要走了 去祈求某个人	赏我份暑期工
Bye.
再见了
Wait!
等下
You could work here at Good Burger.
你可以在美味汉堡工作
Here?
这里
Yeah.
是啊
Hey, Mr. Bailey!
嘿 贝利先生
This guy needs a job.
这个家伙需要份工作
Could he have one?
能给个他吗
No!
不能
See ya.
再见
Wait,wait,wait.
等等 等等 等等
Come on, Mr. Bailey.
拜托了 贝利先生
He really needs one.
他真的需要一份
He can do fries.
他可以负责油炸
Otis does fries.
欧迪斯负责这个
Yeah, but look at him.
但是瞧瞧他
How much longer could he possibly live?
他还能坚持工作多久呢
Well... Have you ever worked in fast food before uh...
好吧 你有在快餐店工作的经验吗
Dexter!
德克斯特
Dexter Reed and yes,
德克斯特 瑞德
I have worked in fast food.
我在快餐店工作过
Yeah? How long?
是吗 多长时间
Nearly two days.
将近两天
Oh, hmm, do you know how to drive a motor vehicle?
额 你会骑摩托车吗
Yes. I'm an excellent driver.
是的 我是个很棒的驾驶员
Any accident on your record?
你有不良记录吗
Not to your knowledge.
就你所知没有
All right, Dexter, I'm gonna give you a shot.
好吧 德克斯特 我会让你试一试
You are on deliveries and you may have to picture and do some cater work.
你负责外卖还有一些点餐服务
Ok.
好的
Cool. I'll teach him everything I know.
酷 我会教他所有我知道的
Oh God help me.
哦 老天
I won't let you down.
我不会让你失望的
Hey, Fizz.
嘿 费兹
This is Dexter.
这是德克斯特
Fizz works drive-threw.
费兹负责跑堂
Wow, Hideo Dexter.
哇哦 你好啊 德克斯特
Hi, Hideo Fizz.
嗨 你好啊 费兹
Hey, wow, nobody's ever reread my name before. I love that.
哇哦 之前都没人会重念我的名字 太棒了
Ha.
哈
Hey, that's Otis. He's 77 years old and still works in fast food.
嘿 那是欧迪斯 他已经77岁了 还一直在快餐业工作
I should have died years ago.
我应该几年前就死了的
Tough, right?
好吧
And there's Deedee. She's a vetinarian.
她是迪迪 她是个素食主义者
Vegetarian.
素食主义者
Oh.
哦
That means she doesn't eat fur.
意思是说他不吃毛皮
I won't wear fur. I don't eat meat.
我不穿皮毛 不吃肉
Hmmmmmmmm
嗯
Hey eh Ed, what, what is that?
嘿 艾德 那是什么 什么状况
Oh, oh, that's just Spatch. Let me show you. Come here.
哦 那是史派驰 让我来介绍 来这边
Hey Spatch.
嘿史派驰
Spatch isn't much of a people person.
史派驰不是个很正常的人
You wanna erase that off?
你要清理下吗
Well, hello, my name is Dextor. I'm your new co-worker.
你好 我叫德克斯特 我是你新的工作伙伴
Monique.
莫妮克
Well that's a nice outfit you get on there.
你穿这套装真好看
There those stripes really break out the color of your eyes.
这些条纹很衬你眼睛的颜色
Yes.
是的
You can imagine how embarrassed I was when I came to work and saw everyone wearing the same thing.
你可以想象我每天走进来看见所有人都穿的一样得有多尴尬
Ha, well, okay, I'll... I guess I'll see you later then.
好吧 我想待会见吧
Guess you will.
我猜你会的
Yo, man, who was that? She is all that.
哟 伙计 她是谁 她拥有全部
All what?
全部什么
Never mind.
没什么了
So tell me, what am I gonna make my deliveries in? A van? A truck?
现在告诉我 我要怎样送外卖呢 货车还是卡车
There she is. The burger mobile. Think you can handle it?
她就是了 汉堡车 你觉得能开吗
I don't know. I've never drive in a sandwich before.
我不知道 我以前从来没开过三明治
Come. I'll take you for a spin.
来吧 我带你去兜风
I...
我
Now em, you can drive, Ed, I mean, you can read all the signs and stuff.
现在你可以开了 艾德 我是说 你都清楚这些标识吧
Yeah! Now this is what I call fast food.
是的 这才是我现在要说的快餐
Wow, wow, wow, hey, look out.
哇哦 小心点
That was a stop sign.
那是个停止标志
No.
不
Watch out for the...
小心
Hey,  come back here.
嘿 回来
Closing time at last.
下班时间了
All right. Let me see,
好吧 让我算算
five dollars an hour, six hours a day, five days a week,
5美元一小时 一天6小时 一周5天
I should be able to pay off the car in a...
我应该能偿还清
Another life time.
在下辈子
Hmm, this place is the most nauseating, pathetical I've ever seen.
嗯 这是我见过最恶心最可怜的地方了
I mean what kind of disease med would you consider eating here?
我是说哪种病人会考虑在这里吃饭呢
Welcome to good burger, home of the good burger, can I take your order, huh?
欢迎光临美味汉堡 美味汉堡之家 你需要点些什么吗
Let's check it boys. Right back there. It's the reject.
瞧瞧那男孩儿 就在那后面 被炒的那个
Hey, check it. It's the Mondo idiot.
嘿 瞧瞧 这是蒙多蠢货
Oh, nice to meet you Mondo idiot, I'm Ed, huh.
哦 很高兴认识你蒙多蠢货 我是艾德
Well, Ed, you'd better watch your butt, man.
艾德 你最好看好你的屁股
Okay.
好吧
Look, you got the purpose for being here.
你已经达到来这里的目的了
Yeah, I do.
是的
I just thought you Good Burger losers should be aware
我只是觉得美味汉堡的失败者应该知道
that tonight is the grand opening of Mondo Burger.
蒙多汉堡今晚盛大开张
The second we open our doors, Good Burger goes in the grinder.
还有就是我们一开张 美味汉堡就会被粉碎
Again with this grinder. Look man, you either order some or you can get out of here.
又是粉碎的梗 伙计 你要不点餐要不滚出这里
Yeah, sure you can take my order.
我确实要你为我点单
I'll have the every last Good Burger to go.
我会带着最后的美味汉堡离开
Oh, I give up. There's no way a guy can watch his own butt.
我放弃了 没人可以看见他自己的屁股
Yeah, is everybody likin' my party?
耶 大家都喜欢我的派对吗
And now, Excite to present you people, Mondo Burger.
现在 大家为蒙多汉堡狂欢吧
Now people welcome to Mondo Burger.
欢迎来到蒙多汉堡
Mr. Belly, since we don't have any costumers or electricity,
贝利先生 既然我们没有任何客人和电
Yeah, yeah. I suppose we should all just going home.
是的 是的 我觉得大家还是回去吧
Looks like Good Burger closed early tonight.
貌似美味汉堡今晚提早关门了
Yep. And I think pretty soon they'll be closed for good.
是啊 而且我确信他们很快会关门大吉的
Everybody, I got one.
伙伴们 我拿到一个
Got one what?
一个什么
What? What?
什么 什么
A Mondo Burger.
一个蒙多汉堡
Oh, let me see it.
哦 让我瞧瞧
All right, all right everybody. Don't get all excitable.
好了好了 别那么激动
Ah.
啊
Huge.
好大啊
Look at that.
瞧瞧
And I don't know how they do it,
我都不知道他们怎么做到的
but they charge the same amount as we do for a Good Burger.
他们和我们卖一样的价格
How do they do it?
他们怎么办到的
Just use more meat.
只是用了更多的肉
Oh, poor cows.
哦 可怜的牛
Hey, Spatch, hand me a Good Burger.
嘿 史派驰给我个美味汉堡
They sound similar.
他们听起来差不多
Come on, what's our take today.
拜托 我们今天卖了多少
43 dollars and 9 cents.
43美元9分
That's it?
就这点
Oh, I suppose I can always feed my mother cat food.
哦 我以为我可以用猫粮给我妈吃
Now probably won't be the right time to ask for a raise, right?
现在也许不是要求加薪的好时机 对吗
No.
不
I'm going home.
我要回家
Good night people.
晚安 大家
Good night Mr. Belly.
晚安 贝利先生
So Monique, what are you going to do tonight after you lock up?
莫妮克 你今晚下班后准备干嘛
I thought I'd go home.
我想我是回家去
Home, why?
回家 为什么
Well, that's where my stuff is.
因为 我所有东西都在那儿
Stuff, ha, ha, ha.
东西 哈 哈 哈
Hey guys, wanna hang out tonight?
嘿 伙计 今晚出去玩吗
Oh no.
不
Hey Ed, you'd  be careful.
嘿 艾德 你得小心点
You.
你
Me?
我
Now I know where I saw you before.
现在我知道我在哪里见过你了
You are the one who blades that cause my accident.
你就是引起我车祸的人
Eh, no?
不
You are the reason why I owe 19,00 bucks.
就是你害我欠下1900美元
You are the reason my mom found out that I was driving without a license.
就是你害我妈妈发现我无证驾驶的
Man, you cost me a fortune.
你害我一无所有
You rack my summer, man, you ruin my life.
你让我的夏天一团糟 毁了我的生活
So, you don't want to hang out tonight?
所以 你今天不出去玩
No, I don't want to hanging out with you ever.
不 我再也不想和你出去了
You think you can get me to a hospital, I think I broke my ass.
你可以送我去医院吗 我应该摔坏屁股了
Come home. Otis.
回家吧 欧迪斯
Get out the way.
让开
Up.
这里走
Oh, man.
哦 天哪
Ah, Mr. Reed. How's working as usual?
瑞德先生 工作如何
I'm having my lunch.
我在吃午饭
Well, I just got my car from the body shop. You gotta admit good as new.
我刚刚取回我的车 不得不说 崭新如初
Here's the receipt.
这是账单
2,500 dollars? No, the estimate was not even 1,900.
2500美元 不 估价不是都不到1900美元吗
Well that is, my younger brother, why they're called an estimate.
年轻人这就是为什么他们说是估价
Close to, kinda, could be?
估价就是接近或者大概
And I have to make you about two and half a month to give me my money.
你得在2个半月内还清全部的钱
Now you have a good day at work and I'm have lunch at Mondo Burger,
现在你好好在这工作
home of big booty burger.
我去蒙多汉堡吃个午饭
Big Booty Burger.
大汉堡
树 屋
字 幕 组
Damn.
混蛋
Mind if I sit here?
我坐这 不介意吧
Yes, I do mind.
我介意
Thanks.
谢谢
What, what are you doing?
你在干嘛
Eating my lunch.
吃午餐啊
郑重声明:本作品之片源、字幕均来自互联网，版权归原电影公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，否则一切后果由该组织或个人承担！本字幕组和制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
I told you not to sit here. I don't like you,
我叫你别坐这儿 我讨厌你
Ain't you get that to your head?
难道你脑子不通吗
I can try.
我试试
Nope.
不通
All right. I see. I'll just have to explain all that myself for you.
好了 我就跟你直说吧
I don't wanna sit by you. I don't wanna see you. I don't wanna smell you.
我不想跟你坐一起 不想看到你 不想闻到你的味道
I don't wanna hanging out with you. I don't even wanna use the word with the letter U.
不想和你一块出去 连你这字我都不想说
Look! I'm grape-nose boy.
看 我的鼻子长葡萄了
Stop that.
别闹
Would you stop?
别闹 好吗
That's very fun.
很有趣 行吧
There he laughed.
笑了吧
So, oh, I give up.
那么 算了
Grape?
你也来一个
Oh, no I'll pass.
不 我算了
I should figure that a lunch with you would be different.
我早该知道跟你吃午餐会有些特别
Hey, what's that dude?
嘿 这是什么
It's my sauce.
我的酱啊
I make it myself.
自己做的自己做的
You carry your own sauce?
你还自带酱
Doesn't everybody?
大家不都带吗
Hey, would you watch it?
嘿 小心点好吗
Sorry.
抱歉
Hey ,that is kind of good.
嘿 尝起来不错
You sure you made it by yourself?
是你自己做的
Yes, my very own recipe.
是啊 我的独家秘方
Nobody knows about this right?
还没人知道你的秘方吧
No.
没有
Hey, Fizz, come here.
嘿 费兹 过来
Hi guys what can I... Hey what do you...
伙计们 怎么了 嘿 你干什么
Hmm, this is really good. What did you guy put on this?
嗯 真不错 你们在里面加了什么
Deedee, Otis, Monique, come here.
迪迪 欧迪斯 莫妮克 快来
Mom,I got to call you back.
妈 我一会儿给你打过去
This is so good.
味道不错
All right, wait, what in the grand name of beef is going on?
等等 到底出什么事了
Mr. Belly try this.
贝利先生 尝尝这个
That's right, I will cut...
好了 给我停下
This is marvelous. What is it?
太好吃了 这是什么
A French fry?
薯条啊
I know that Ed, I'm talking about the sauce.
埃德 我知道 我说的是酱
What's in the sauce?
用的什么酱料
It's an ingredients he made himself.
他自己配的酱料
- Ed?   - This is excellent.
-埃德做的   -太棒了
This is awesome.
棒极了
It makes me glad that I'm not dead.
还好我还没死 能吃到这美味
Ed, If we put this sauce on all the Good Burgers,
埃德 如果我们把你的酱加到美味汉堡里去
then everyone would wanna eat here.
那每个人都会来这吃的
We'll wipe Mondo Burger right after map.
我们会把蒙多汉堡赶得远远的
Great. That's great.
好 太好了
Ed, get in that kitchen and start making the sauce.
埃德 去厨房 开始做酱吧
Yep is Yeppy
谨遵命令
Go ahead.
行动吧
They shall be done
保证完成任务
Give me a little French fries.
再给我来点薯条
Good Burger is back in business.
美味汉堡重回江湖
Yeah.
耶
Ed, I never see some of these customers. Good Burger is back in business.
埃德 我从没见过来这么多顾客 美味汉堡重回江湖
Oh, back in business.
重回江湖
Move over Mondo Burger.
甩蒙多汉堡好几条街
Move over.
甩好几条街
Ed, whatever Good Burger we sell,
埃德 不管卖多少汉堡
I'll give you 10 cents for every one.
每个汉堡我给你10美分抽成
Yeah.
耶
A little help here?
能帮我下吗
Oh, Ok.
噢 好的
No, no, no, no, no. I'll help Dee.
不用 不用 我帮迪迪
You get in that kitchen and keep making sauce.
你去厨房继续做酱吧
Well, Ed how's that sauce making coming along?
埃德 酱做的怎么样啦
Pretty good, Mr. Belly says it gonna save Good Burger.
还行 贝利先生说我的酱会拯救美味汉堡
That's great.
很好
Now you do remember that it was my idea to put the sauce on the Good Burgers in the first place right?
你应该记得是我最先想到把你的酱加到美味汉堡里去的吧
Yeah. You should get some of the money I received.
记得 你应该从我这里分点抽成
I'm glad to hear you say that.
很高兴听你这么说
In fact, since we gonna be in business together,
其实 既然我们重振雄风了
I thought maybe we should sign a little contract, just make our partnership official.
我想我们应该签个小合同 这样我们的合作也正式点
Okay.
好啊
Hmm
嗯哼
Oh, yeah.
欧耶
I know some of these words.
我看懂了一些词
So what's it all mean Dexter?
整个说的什么意思啊 德克斯特
Well, it's quite simple, really.
很简单 真的
Of all the money that Good Burger make using your sauce,
美味汉堡给你的抽成中
you get to keep 20%, cool? Okay? Then I'll keep the other 80%.
你留20% 怎么样 我抽80%
So it works out cool for both of us.
这样对我俩最好
Okay.
行
Here you go.
签好了
Cool, all right.
好 就这样
Ed, there must be 50 customers out there.
埃德 外面肯定有50多位的顾客
It's unbelievable. What did you put in that sauce?
真不敢相信 你往酱里放什么呢
Well, you start with some lemon juice and some ketchup...
先放点柠檬汁 再放点番茄汁
Look Dexter, you and I are friends but I have ...
德克斯特 我俩是朋友 但是
No, listen to me carefully.
你认真听我说
Okay.
好
Do not tell anyone the recipe to your sauce.
别把你的酱料秘方告诉任何人
Oh, first you start off with some lemon juice...
噢 首先 你先放点柠檬汁
Stop it. Stop talking.
停 别说了
Never tell anyone the ingredients of your sauce.
别跟任何人说你的酱料秘方
Why?
为什么
You wanna save Good Burger, don't you?
你想拯救美味汉堡吗 想吗
Oh, yeah. Good Burger is my life.
当然了 美味汉堡就是我的命啊
Well then, you gotta keep you sauce recipe a secret, all right?
那就别说 把它当做秘密 好吗
Okay. Dexter, you squeezed in my pancreas.
好 德克斯特 你压着我肚子了
Sorry.
对不起
Thanks.
谢谢
Unbelievable. Two days ago, we had Good Burger crushed.
想不到 两天前 我们还把美味汉堡整的很惨
Now look at them.
现在你看
I think it's the sauce, boss.
应该是酱料的原因 老板
I know that.
我知道
You think you're stupid?
你们是不是傻
I want Good Burger out of business.
我想要美味汉堡倒闭
Go find out what's in that sauce.
去找出酱料里有什么
I'll go get some and have them checked out.
我去弄一些然后查出来
Ed, here's your take for today, 67dollars.
埃德 这是你今天的抽成  67美元
Yeah.
耶
Thanks for the sauce kid.
谢谢你的酱 孩子
Love you
爱死你了
Here you go Ed, you get to keep 13 dollars.
接着 埃德 你得13美元
Well that's almost 14 dollars.
哇 差不多有14美元呢
Yep, well, see you tomorrow.
是啊 明天见
Hey, Dexter, what are you doing? Do you wanna hanging out and do something?
嘿 德克斯特 你在干嘛呢 想一起出去逛下吗
Gee, I don't know. I gotta go and clean my room. I gotta...
不知道啊 我要回家打扫房间 我
Please?
走嘛
Sure, let's hanging out.
好 我们走吧
Cool.
很好
Wanna see my secret place?
想看看我的秘密基地吗
That's not what I having in mind.
我想的可不是那个
Come on.
来嘛
All right. I'll get you...
好吧 下班接你
This is my place. This is where I come to think,
这就是我的基地 我想事情的地方
well I think
我思考
It's funny, I never took you too much of a thinker.
好吧 我从没把你当作一个思考者
I have to say that I think of all kinds of things.
我得说我思考过所有的事情
Good Burger, squirrels, Caber board boxes, things that are sticky.
美味汉堡啊 松鼠啊 碳板箱 还有黏黏的东西
I bet you don't have one real problem.
我敢肯定你没有什么真的麻烦
I got six toes on my left foot.
我左脚有六个脚趾头
What kind of problem do you have?
你有什么样的麻烦呢
Other than the one you caused? Lots.
除了你惹的那个麻烦吗 还有 很多呢
Most of them started when I was a little kid.
大多麻烦都从我小时候开始
That's when my dad left me and my mom.
那时我爸离开了我和妈妈
He must have lived in 50 places since then.
他从那以后搬了有50次家
I remember the last time I saw my dad,
我记得我最后一次看到我爸爸
I was 7 years old, and for no reason at all, he bought me this yo-yo.
我那时7岁 不知什么原因 他给我买了个悠悠球
It was so cool. I mean, it wasn't just an ordinary yo-yo.
很棒 它不是普通的悠悠球
It has lights that lit up when you yo-yoed it,
上面还有灯 当你玩的时候还会闪
red lights on one side and blue lights on the other.
一边是红灯 一边是蓝灯
It made this funky whistling voice too.
边转还边发出风笛声
Wow, that sounds like quite a yo-yo. You still got it?
哇 听起来真是特别的悠悠球呢 还在吗
No, after a while it stopped lighting up and making the funky whistling voice,
不在了 玩了段时间 灯也不闪了 风笛声也没了
And I guess my mom has thrown it away.
我猜应该是我妈把它扔了
You know, I don't even remember what my dad looks like.
我甚至不记得我爸长什么样子了
I don't even remember what my dad looks like either,
我也不记得我爸什么样子了
but at least I get to see him everyday.
但我至少每天都能见他
I give up, I'm going home.
算了 我回家了
Hey, Dex. Thanks for hanging out with me.
嘿 德克 谢谢你陪我
It's no problem. See you tomorrow, buddy.
没什么 明天见 兄弟
You mean it?
你是认真的
Mean what?
什么认真的
Well, I mean buddy, you called me your buddy.
兄弟 你叫我兄弟
Yeah, sure, I guess so. See you tomorrow.
当然了 明天见吧
Dexter you got a delivery, you are going to freak.
德克斯特 有个外卖要送 你会大吃一惊的
Hey, Monique. I am just checking.
嘿 莫妮克 我刚看到
I got a delivery. You wanna a ride with me?
我要送个外卖 你想和我一起去吗
I wanna go. I wanna go.
我想 我想
Yeah, you can go, Ed..
你去吧 埃德
Oh, man.
哦 老天
Ed, You have got to park the burger. Slow down.
埃德 你得停好汉堡车 慢点
Come on, man. Lock room this way.
快点 老兄 这边堵了 往这边
So, after scoring a amazing last-minute game winning shot
在经历了最后时刻的绝杀
and bringing your team all the way to the NBA championship, how do you feel?
并带领队伍拿到NBA冠军后 你感觉如何
I feel hungry.
我感觉饿了
Delivery.
外卖
Shaq.
鲨鱼
Here is your good burger.
这是你叫的美味汉堡
Little man, I ordered tomatoes on this burger, I don't see no tomatoes.
小伙子 我有说在汉堡里加西红柿 没看见啊
Hang on. Consider yourself tomato.
稍等 享受你的西红柿吧
You are not like other people, are you?
你总与众不同对吧
Go ahead, Shaq, take a bite of the good burger and tell us how you like the good sauce.
吃吧 大鲨鱼 咬一口我们的美味汉堡 告诉大家我们的酱怎么样
Taste good, pretty good.
好吃 不错
You heard it here, folks, Shaquille O'neal, the man who enjoys good food.
各位都听到了 大鲨鱼奥尼尔 一个爱美食的人
Look, Dexter, we are on live TV.
看啊 德克斯特 我们上电视了
Welcome to good burger, home of good burger.
欢迎来美味汉堡店 美味汉堡之家
Can I take your order?
你需要点什么
I have never been on TV before.
我从没上过电视
I am dude. She's a dude. We are a dude.
我是个伙计 她是个伙计 我们都是伙计
I'm sick. It's puked. Shut up.
受不了 真想吐 闭嘴吧
You are not so fast with the trash talk now, are you, huh?
你还没到说这种大话的时候呢
You got him that time, bro.
你上回就打败他们了
But you haven't noticed, good burger is still in business.
但你没注意到 美味汉堡还在热销呢
What are we supposed to do about it?
我们要怎么做呢
Our burgers are already twice the size as theirs.
我们的汉堡已经做成他们的两倍大了
Kitchen.
厨房
Yes, sir.
是 先生
Make our burgers bigger.
把汉堡再做大点
Bigger? But they are already.
再大点 他们已经
Bigger, bigger.
再大点 再大点
Now let's see good burgers go against burgers three times the size of their own.
让我们看看美味汉堡怎么对抗我们三倍大的汉堡
Great. But what about the Ed sauce?
很好 但埃德的酱要怎么搞到呢
Hey, I am a dude. He is a dude. She is a dude. And we are all d...
我是个伙计 他是个伙计 她是个伙计 我们都是伙计
Welcome to good burger, home of the good burgers, can I take your order?
欢迎来美味汉堡 美味汉堡之家 你需要点什么
You all right, bro?
你还好吗
Hey, I know you. You are the dude from Mondo burger.
嘿 我认识你 你是蒙多汉堡的人
Correct Mondo, her boss as well.
没错 蒙多 我是老板
No, no, no, I am Ed.
不 不 我是埃德
Can I give you a lift, Ed?
我载你吧 埃德
I don't know, dude. I weight about 150.
我不知道 我有150斤重
Just get in the car.
进来就好了
Car?
进车
Yeah.
对
Ed, I am gonna cut right to the chase.
埃德 我有话就直说了
You have been working in good burgers now for like what?
你在美味汉堡工作多久了
Three years? And your manager still only pays you 5 bucks an hour, man.
三年对吗 你经理还只给你5美元一小时
Really? Cool.
是吗 不错啊
Well, 5 bucks an hour is cool. How does 10 bucks sound? Ten bucks.
5美元一小时还行 那10美元听起来如何 10美元
I don't know. Sounds sort of like clack, clack.
不知道 听起来咯吱 咯吱的
I want you to bail on good burger, and I want you to come work for me at Mondo burger.
我希望你辞了美味汉堡的活儿 来蒙多汉堡为我工作
You make your sauce for Kurt.
你来为柯特做酱
Who's Kurt?
谁是科特
I'm Kurt.
我是科特
I'm Ed.
我是埃德
I am aware.
我知道
You said you were Kurt.
你说你是科特（埃德以为aware也是个名字）
Well, thanks for the ride.
谢谢你载我
Whenever you are ready to come work for me, you say the word.
你想什么时候好来我这儿工作 说一声就行
OK.
好
What were you doing in Kurt's car?
你坐科特的车里干嘛
You know just pushing buttons and hanging out.
只是按按车里的按钮 逛逛而已
What did he say to you?
他跟你说什么了
Something about working in Mondo burger.
他说要我去蒙多汉堡工作之类的
I think he likes me.
他挺喜欢我的
Ed, that deep-down does not like you. He just wants to use you.
埃德 他其实不是喜欢你 只是想利用你
That's not natural.
那可不大好
No, he wants your sauce.
他是需要你的酱料
Don't tell him the sauce receipt, all right.
别告诉他酱料秘方 好吗
Because if you do, Good burger is going to be in big trouble.
因为你要是说了 美味汉堡就有大麻烦了
OK.
好
All right. Let's get to work.
那我们去工作吧
All right.
好的
Dexter, I got you something.
德克斯特 我送你个东西
What's this?
什么啊
It's a yo-yo. I bought it with the 13 dollars you gave me.
悠悠球 我用你给我的13美元买的
It lights up and flicks and everything, just like the one your dad gave you.
它会闪 会弹 功能齐备 就像你爸以前给你买的那个
Why did you get this for me?
你为什么送我这个
Cause we are buds.
因为我们是兄弟啊
What's with this dude?
那家伙怎么说
He doesn't want to work in Mondo burger.
他不想来蒙多汉堡工作
If you ask me, this guy is a few taco short of a combination plate.
要我说的话 这家伙就是个傻蛋
I don't care.
我不管这些
Now, Kurt's going to get his sauce.
科特就要他的酱
He does not come this far to listen to some tired craps with good burger get in my way.
他不希望听到美味汉堡挡我们财路这些话的
Bringing Recksel.
叫洛克萨尔过来
If anyone can get the sauce out of Ed, she can.
只有她 才能让弄到埃德的酱料
Excuse me. Hello?
打扰了 你好
Welcome to good burger, home of the good burger. Can I take your order?
欢迎来美味汉堡 美味汉堡之家 你需要点什么
No, thanks. I just came here to see you, Ed.
不 谢谢 我只是来见你的 埃德
I'm Recksel.
我叫洛克萨尔
Oh, welcome to good burger, home of the good burger. Can I take your order?
欢迎来美味汉堡 美味汉堡之家 你需要点什么
You are so hot.
你真热啊（也有性感的意思）
Oh, well, I often sweat at work.
噢 我工作时候常出汗
So, are you hungry?
你饿了吗
Yes, I'm hungry. But not for food. I am hungry for you.
是的 我饿了 不过不是想吃东西 我想要你
Well, I'm not eatable.
我可不能吃
How would you like to go on a date tomorrow night?
你说明晚一起约会如何
With whom?
和谁
Me, silly.
我啊 傻瓜
Me, silly too.
我 也傻瓜
No, I mean that you and I should go out tomorrow night. You want to?
不是 我说你和我明晚一起出去玩 怎么样
Ok, cool.
好啊
Awesome. Here's my address. I'll see you at 8.
很好 这是我的地址 8点见
I don't believe what I just saw.
真不敢相信我刚看见的
Who, Elvis?
谁啊 猫王吗
No, a beautiful girl just throw in here and asked you for a date.
不 我看见一个美女走进来 约你出去
I know. You wanna come?
知道了 你也想去吗
No, three is a crime, man.
不了 三人约会是个罪过
Just bring a date. Hey, why don't you ask Monique?
你带个女伴啊 嘿 你为何不叫莫妮克呢
I don't think so.
别叫了
You know you like her.
你喜欢她啊
How could I not like her?
我怎么会不喜欢她呢
I mean, she is smart, funny, beautiful and cuddly.
她聪明又有趣 漂亮又可爱
Then just ask her out.
那就约她啊
No.
别了
What? You chicken?
什么 你这个胆小鬼
I am not a chicken.
我不是胆小鬼
Are dude. Dexter is a chicken. Chicken. Moo.
就是 德克斯特胆小鬼 胆小鬼
I am not a chicken.
我不是
It's just that I don't think she wants to waste her time going out with me. That's all.
我只是认为她不会花时间和我一起出去的
Moo.
哞
Chickens. Chickens don't moo, man. They cock.
小鸡不是这么叫的 它们咯咯叫 好吗
Hey, Monique, we are all going out tomorrow night.
嘿 莫妮克 我们明晚要出去玩呢
You wanna be Dexter's date.
你做德克斯特的女伴如何
I told you.
我跟你说过
I'd love to.
好啊
I knew she'd say yes.
我就知道她会答应的
Moo!
哞
Corn dog.
来个玉米热狗
Your chair, madam.
请坐 女士
Thank you, Dexter.
谢谢 德克斯特
Your chair.
请坐
Is your butt OK?
屁股疼不疼
It's fine, thank you.
还好 谢谢
It's OK, people. Her butt is fine.
没事儿 各位 她屁股不疼
It's a great corn dog.
这个玉米热狗很棒啊
I wonder how they get the wienie to the corny exterior
我很想知道他们怎么把玉米皮包到香肠外面的
A question that played mankind for centuries.
这是困扰了人们几个世纪的问题
You know what'd go great on these corn dogs?
你知道什么比玉米热狗还要伟大吗
A turtle neck?
乌龟脖子吗
No, silly. Some of your sauce.
不 傻瓜 是你的酱料啊
I just love your sauce. How do you make it? I'm dying to know.
我很喜欢你的酱 你怎么做的 我很想知道
First you start off with some ketchup and some lemon juice.
你先放些番茄酱 再加点柠檬汁儿
Oops.
哦哟
What's matter? Is it your butt?
怎么了 你屁股疼吗
No.
不
What do you say we start a putter?
我们要不去玩高尔夫推杆吧
I get to go first.
我先去玩
Come on, Recksel.
走吧 洛克萨尔
Ed, can we just go somewhere and be alone?
埃德 我们要不单独去个什么地方吧
What for?
去干嘛
Well, maybe we could talk, maybe get to know each other a little better.
我们可以聊聊啊 也许可以更深入地了解对方
Doesn't that sound a little more fun than miniature golf?
那样不比打迷你高尔夫更有意思吗
No, come on.
不了 走吧
So close, yet so far.
差一点 又差不止一点
My turn, excuse me, thank you  very much.
到我了 让我下 非常感谢
All righty, oh.
好了
So, is this your first time.
这是你第一次玩吗
Well, keep talking.
好吧 尽管笑我吧
My turn.
到我了
Your turn.
到你了
Then when I was 6, I said my first words, my mom thinks it was trousers.
我6岁的时候才开始说话 我妈说那是裤子
But I think it was tweezers, then I went to...
但我说它是镊子 后来
Ed, she is still unconscious, bro.
埃德 她还昏迷着呢
What happened?
怎么了
Your head hit my golf ball. Then you went sleepy by.
你的头撞到了我的高尔夫球 后来你就睡过去了
Monique, you wanna take a walk?
莫妮克 你要一起走走吗
Sure.
好啊
Wait, what am I supposed to do?
等等 那我要干什么呢
Hello?
这里啊
Hello. What am I supposed to do?
你好 我要干什么呢
Ed, I think Recksel gonna help you figure something out.
埃德 洛克萨尔会帮你想出来的
So, Ed, what do you wanna do?
埃德 你想做什么呢
Well, I always want to shave a Martian, got a Martian?
我总是想去给火星人刮胡须 你有火星人吗
Here you go.
穿好
Thank you.
谢谢
So, you like me?
那么 你喜欢我吗
Of course.
当然
So, you like me?
那你喜欢我吗
Are you kidding me? I like you from the first time I saw you.
开玩笑吗 我第一次看见你就喜欢上你了
Right off the back. But I guess it was the same for you too.
还是看你背影时候 不过我想你应该也有这感觉
No, I think you were self-centered and obnoxious.
不 其实我认为你是个以我为中心 有点讨厌的人
Well, so much for my self-esteem.
好吧 说够了我的自大了吧
I changed my mind, didn't I?
我改变了我的看法 不是吗
Yes, you did. How come?
是 怎么改变的
Ed.
是埃德
Excuse me.
没懂
Ed thinks you were a great guy.
埃德认为你是个好人
He is always talking about what a great friend you are to him
他总是说你是个他的好朋友
and what a nice person you are.
说你多么好多么好
Really? Ed said all that?
真的 埃德那么说吗
Ed is the sweetest, most generous person I have ever met.
埃德是我见过的最可爱 最善良的人
And anybody he likes so much can't be all bad.
他认为不错的人不会差到哪里去
Look at me, Ed.
看着我 埃德
I am looking.
看着呢
What do you see?
你看见了什么
That big red lump on your forehead with a golf ball hit on you.
你额头上被高尔夫球打到的红印
Look into my eyes, Ed, tell me how you make your sauce.
看着我的眼睛 埃德 告诉我你是怎么做酱料的
And I'll give you anything you want.
我会给你任何你想要的东西
What did you got?
你有什么呢
For starters, how about this?
那么先这样如何
Oh, no.
噢 不
Sorry, you surprised me.
对不起 你惊着我了
Can you breathe?
你能呼吸吗
I quit.
我不干了
I am guessing she didn't get the sauce receipt.
我猜她没弄到秘方
I am aware.
我知道
Hello, my name is Carmon Lou.
你好 我叫卡尼蒙•露
I am hosting a family reunion at my oven house for a Mark.
我正在我家弄个家庭聚会
I think it's a heater actually.
我认为聚会还行
Anywho, I'd like to order three good meals for dinner good meals
谁来给我点个三份主食
and 17 resort of your food chunks.
17份点心
OK, I told you the good meals.
好 我来给你说下主食
I need to substitute the good cookie for the good pie.
我要好吃的饼干来配好的派
Don't fry the extra, I'll pony up the baverage.
不要把薯条炸的太老了 一般般就好了
On the regular good meals.
中量的餐是这样
I need two of the good burgers to have ketchup, lettuce, tomato, but no onion.
我要2个汉堡 加番茄酱 生菜 西红柿 不要洋葱
I've got an interview this afternoon.
我下午有一个面试
Let's see, that takes care of everyone but uncle Les,
我想想 这样就照顾到了每个人 除了莱斯叔叔
who doesn't eat meat, but of course he does eat dairy.
他不吃肉 不过当然 他吃乳制品的
So, I don't get it, Ed.
那么这样 埃德
Let get Les a good chicken with some good fries and some good lettuce.
给莱斯叔叔来点鸡肉 再加薯条 还有生菜
All good to go. But I'd like to have my beverage by my weight.
就是这样 我要控制体重 就来点饮料吧
Now, total me up.
好了 给我打包吧
Guess who?
猜猜我是谁
Hey, Dexter.
嘿 德克斯特
What are you doing?
在干嘛呢
Getting ready for work.
准备工作
Cool, cool. Listen, since we had such nice time last night,
好 既然咱们昨晚过得挺愉快
I thought maybe we can do it again tonight.
我想也许今晚再一块约会吧
I don't think so.
我可不这么想
OK, tomorrow night, maybe?
好吧 那明晚吧
No.
不
Maybe this weekend?
那这周末
Maybe not
不了
OK, who are you? What have you done with the real Monique?
好吧 你到底是谁 你对那个真正的莫妮克做了什么
Oh, she's right here. It's just now she knows the real Dexter.
我就是我 只是现在我认识了真正的德克斯特
Come again.
再说一遍
Forgot your jacket last night.
你昨晚忘拿你的夹克了
Thank you.
谢谢
And this fell out the pocket.
还有这个 从夹克里掉了出来
This is just all it is.
噢 就是这个事啊
Fine, it's just a contract you had Ed signed.
好 这不过就是个你让埃德签的合同好吧
You know, the one you take most of his money,
你拿走了他多半的抽成
the money he's supposed to get by his sauce.
这本是他靠酱料该得到的钱
No, yeah, but, look, I was just trying to.
不 听着 我正准备要
I can't believe you would do something like that to someone who trusts you.
我不敢相信你居然对信任你的人做这样的事儿
How can you take advantage of a sweet person like Ed.
你怎么能利用像埃德这样好的人呢
And after he got you a job?
他还帮你找了工作
What the. I only wanted.
什么 我只是想
Oh, I know what you wanted.
噢 我知道你想什么
You're not Ed's friend.
你不是埃德的朋友
You are just using him to scam a little cash on the side.
你只是利用他来弄点钱花
That must felt really good.
你这么做一定很开心
But don't worry, I am not going to tell Ed that you are cheating him.
不过别担心 我不会告诉埃德你在骗他
Why not?
为什么不
Cause it'd hurt him too much.
因为这会太伤他的心
Punk.
傻瓜啊
There you are, Ed. Can I sit here?
你在这儿呢 埃德 我能坐这儿吗
On my lap?
坐我大腿上吗
No, man. I'll just sit down right next to you.
不 我坐你旁边而已
All right, look, Ed, I don't know how to say this.
听着 埃德 我不知道怎么跟你说
Oh, you just go say--------s.
噢 你就这样说 嘶
No, I am talking about this contract.
不是 我是要说合同的事儿
What is it, boy? What?
怎么了 狗狗 什么
Four clowns, their car's broken down. They are in trouble.
四个小丑 他们的车抛锚了 他们遇到麻烦了
Ed, that dog is not talking to you.
埃德 这狗没在和你说话
Wait, hang on.
等等
He's trying to tell us that there's four clowns stuck somewhere and their car broke down.
它想告诉我们四个小丑的车抛锚了 被困在哪里呢
Where, boy, where?
他们在哪里 哪里
Ed, there are no clowns. Man that dog is just hungry.
埃德 没有小丑 那只狗只是饿了
Maybe we should feed him.
也许我们该喂喂它
Here, have a Mondo burger.
给你 吃一个蒙多汉堡
He's not eating it. What's wrong?
没吃 有什么不对吗
I don't know.
不知道
He definitely looks hungry though.
它看起来绝对是饿了
Here, try a Good burger.
给你 吃个美味汉堡
well, you look at that.
你看呐
See? I told you there was something wrong with the mondo burger.
看见没 我就说蒙多汉堡有问题
He knows it. Don't you, boy?
他知道 对吧 狗狗
He definitely senses something he doesn't like.
它肯定感觉到其中有古怪了
what do you think it might be?
你认为会是什么呢
I don't know. Let's find out.
不知道 我们一起找出来吧
where is that damn dog?
那只死狗去哪儿了
Excuse me ladies. My I help you?
女士们 请问有什么需要吗
Can you kindly point us the direction of the little girls room?
你能告诉我洗手间在哪吗
Yes, Ma'am. The ladies' room is just on the other side of the restaurant.
没问题 女士 洗手间在餐馆的另一边
I'll show you.
我带你去
Awww! Get your hands off me.
啊啊啊 拿开你的咸猪手
I'm just trying to help.
我只是想帮助你
I don't need your hel... oh..
我不需要你的帮 噢
Ohoh...
噢
Water! Water! Water! I need water.
水 水 我要水
树 屋
字 幕 组
Awww water! Water! Water!
啊 水 快给我水
OH~ Water...Oh~ Water...
我要水
Ok. I'll be right back.
我去拿水 马上回来
郑重声明:本作品之片源、字幕均来自互联网，版权归原电影公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，否则一切后果由该组织或个人承担！本字幕组和制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
All right, Let's go
好了 我们走吧
Wait! What about you water?
等一下 那你要的水怎么办
You just come on!
你跟我来就够了
hey, what's that stuff they are dropping onto the burgers?
快看 那个人在汉堡里放了什么呀
I don't know.
我也不知道
But I bet that's what makes those burgers grow so big.
但是我猜就是那东西让汉堡膨胀得那么大的
we need to get some of those stuff for good burger.
我们也需要在美味汉堡里放点那东西 哈哈
Oh, Man. Stuff like that got to be illegal.
伙计 那个东西是违法的
It is illegal.
这是违法的
Thrampathol is way illegal.
使用膨胀剂是违法的
But I'll tell you what,
但我告诉你
it surely makes burgers nicer and in-normal.
这个绝对可以让汉堡以不正常的方式变得更诱人
Oh yeah! That's all really good.
是 这样确实很不错
But what happens to those nice innocent people
但是那些吃了你们不正常汉堡的无辜的人们
when they eat your in-normal burgers.
会怎么样呢
Ah-oh.
啊哦
Don't care, ladies!
女士们 我才不关心呢
Yeah, yeah! Laugh it up.
呵呵 尽情地笑吧
When those people find out that you put illegal stuff in their meat,
但是当大家发现你们在肉里加了违法的东西
you will find yourself in jail.
你们会被送进监狱的
That's why
这就是为什么
nobody outside this kitchen is gonna find out.
厨房以外的人都不会发现这个秘密的原因了
What do you expect us to do? To keep our mouths shut?
那你想让我们怎么闭上我们的嘴呢
NO. I will keep your mouths shut.
不 我会让你们闭嘴的
Ed, run!
埃德 快跑
Ok hot pants.
穿热裤的傻瓜
Now I am tired of playing games.
现在我厌倦了跟你们玩游戏
I want to know what's in your sauce.
我要知道你酱料的配方
You can forget it!
别想了
You are not gonna get Ed's sauce.
你不会得到埃德酱料配方的
I want to know what's in your sauce.
我要知道 你的 酱料配方
Dude...
伙计
you need a Tic Tac.
你得吃颗薄荷糖了 你口气好臭
Let's kayos it. You guys are grass.
击败他们 他们不堪一击
What are we gonna do with them?
我们要怎么对付他们呢
Get our Power Way on the phone.
打个电话 把他们送到我们的秘密基地去
Demented Hills?
疯狂的山坡吗
Easy man, easy.
放松点 放松
You mustn't have known where my mom worked.
我才不怕呢 你们肯定不知道我妈在哪儿工作的
Hey man. Let us go.
喂喂 大哥 放我们走
I am not gonna tell you again.
我不会再说一次的
Alright, maybe I'll tell you one more time.
好吧 也许我应该再告诉你一次
Open this door, please?
拜托 开开门
Look, Derek.
德雷克 你看
The walls are padding. Look what I can do.
墙是软的 我可以横冲直撞
I don't get it. I just don't get it.
我不明白 实在是不明白
Where could they be?
他们会在哪里呢
I'm really worried, you guys.
我真的很担心他们俩
Hi.
嗨
I'm psychopath.
我是精神病人
I'm Ed.
我是埃德
Have small space aliens ever landed in your brain
有没有小外星人在你的脑袋里
and told you to break into the zoo for the kangaroos?
告诉你去闯进动物园找袋鼠
Not that I recall.
没有
Do you think I'm cute?
你认为我可爱吗
Sure. Haha.
当然咯
What's cute about me?
我哪里可爱呢
hmmm, you head?
额 你的脑袋
You have a cute head too.
你的脑袋也很可爱
hehe, well. I try to keep it nice.
我试着让它变得好看点
So what are you here for?
你来这里干什么
I got into trouble for breaking into the zoo
我闯进动物园放走了所有的袋鼠
and freeing all the kangaroos.
然后就被抓进来了
My name is Heather.
我叫海瑟
Really? My mom's name is Heather
真的吗 我妈也叫海瑟
Really?
真的吗
No...
不是
I like you, Ed.
我喜欢你 埃德
Hmmm...
额
Go fish.
钓鱼（一种纸牌游戏）
Would you stop eating the card.
麻烦你别再吃牌了好吗
And quit poking me!	Are you crazy?
你别戳我了 你疯了吗
Man...
天呀
Why am I playing card with these folks.
为什么我在跟这些家伙打牌玩
Ewww... nasty.
脏死了
Hey, dude.
嘿 哥们
They got me a jacket just like that.
他们也给了我一件跟你一样的外套
Need some help?
需要什么帮助吗
look out!
当心
open it!
打开它
There is a fridge. Look for the sauce, dude.
这里有个冰箱 兄弟们 去找酱料
Got it.
找到了
What's going on in here?
谁在那里 在干什么
Stop waving that tiny light in my face.
别拿小手电筒照着我的脸
Who are you?
你是谁
Let me ask. Who are you?
应该是我问你们是谁
Relax. The old guy that works here.
放松点 这是在这工作的老家伙
What are doing here this late?
这么晚了 你还在这里干嘛
Sleep until you woke me up.
你们吵醒我之前 我在睡觉
What's that junk you pouring into our sauce?
你们往我们的酱料里倒了什么
Shut up old man.
闭嘴 臭老头
Don't be rude to the elderly.
别对老人家无礼
The old man asked us a question.
这位老人家问了我们一个问题呢
Now,it's called shark poison.
这个叫做鲨鱼毒药
It's just may cause
这个可以让
your little good burger customers very very sick.
吃了美味汉堡的顾客非常的虚弱
So sick that I doubt anybody would want to eat at here ever again.
虚弱到吃了美味汉堡的人不会再来光顾你们这破地方了
I'm calling the cops.
我要打电话报警
You are not calling anyone.
别想打给任何人
There you go. Join your buddies.
去吧 跟你的好兄弟们待在一起
Otis. You come to visit huh?
欧迪斯 你来看我们了吗
I'm fine, and you?
我很好 你呢
Help me get him out of this.
帮我给他解开这个
Do I look like I came to visit?
我看起来像是来看望你们的吗
Where am I? What's going on?
我这是在哪里 发生了什么
They kidnapped us. Why they bring you here?
他们绑架了我们 他们为什么把你也抓进来了
Because I caught those Mondo rats
因为我抓到蒙多汉堡的人
damping shark poison in our sauce.
往我们的酱料里倒鲨鱼毒药
Shark poison?
鲨鱼毒药
I don't understand why they'd harm those innocent sharks.
我不明白他们为什么要伤害无辜的鲨鱼
Will you forget about the sharks?
不要再说鲨鱼了
This stuff is gonna hurt innocent people.
这个毒药会害到许多无辜的人
Can you get to a phone?
你能找得着电话吗
There is no chance.
这里根本没电话
Got to get out of this place...
我们得离开这个地方
What time is it?
现在什么时候了
I'll tell you.
我来告诉你
6 a.m. Good burger opens at 10.
现在是早上六点 美味汉堡十点钟开门营业
Look like we only got 4 hours to warn them.
我们要在四小时内逃出去提醒大家
But how are we gonna get out of here?
但是我们怎么逃出去呢
Just let me handle that part.
让我来想想办法吧
Good morning patients!
早安 病人们
It's medication time!
现在是用药时间了
I will be back in 10 minutes
十分钟内我就会
with your various prescriptions.
带着大家的药回来
That music sucks
这个音乐糟糕透了
It does. Hang on!
是很糟糕 等我一下
Hey dude, I'll be right back.
嘿 哥们 我马上回来
Where are you going?
你要去哪里
Ed? Ed?
埃德 埃德
I don't think you should touch it up.
我觉得你最好不要碰
On the radio dot...
录音机的按钮
Come on! Dance with me! Come on!
来吧 跟我一起跳舞吧
Come on. Everybody.
大家一起跳起来
Yeah. Let's have some fun. Cool.
一起嗨起来
Hey, check out the cools.
嘿 看看 他们跳得还不错嘛
I'd say same.
确实还不错
There's something about it
有一些事情
she always makes me dance...
她总是让我情不自禁地舞动起来
on and on and on.
一直跳舞 无法停止
Never miss up a beat.
从不错过一个节拍
Boy, wasn't it neat?
男孩 离女孩很近吧
Yeah...
耶...
She's a freak. The girl that never missed up a beat.
她是个怪人 她从来不错过一个节拍
Never losing a beat.
从不失去一个节拍
hey, how are you doing?
嘿 你们怎么样
All righty!
好吧
Is was a volcano...
她是一座热情的火山
I bet you guys got your moves huh?
我猜你们也想跟着一起跳吧
I really can't do that...
不 我真的不能跳
NO... I am not good at that.
对呀 我很不擅长跳舞
Awww... come on...You know you get ...
哎呀 一起跳嘛 你们肯定
NO, we got regulations.
不行 我们有规定的
See? You found them in your head.
看 你也想跳吧
Yeah! Let's have fun.
对 让我们一起嗨起来
we got to go!
我们得走了
Come out.
快出去
Easy...
放松点
In here!
就是这里
I think I pick the bad room...
我想我选错了房间
Just don't make any sane moves.
不要轻举妄动
What's up dude? Give me five.
哥们儿 你怎么样 我们击个掌吧
On the blackened side. Huh~ yeah
换一面击一个 哈哈
I can't believe that you make friends with these psychopath...
想不到你居然跟这些精神病人交上朋友了
Attention! Seal all safety doors.
注意 马上关上所有的安全门
Can we open these windows?
我们能打开这些窗户吗
No you can't.
你打不开的
They are medically sealed with triple thick bullet proof glass.
他们在窗户上加了三层很厚的防弹玻璃
Mr. Hugh Garyman, could you open up one of these windows?
休•格雷曼先生 能麻烦你打开这些窗户吗
Cool. Go ahead.
太好了 你来吧
Awww, man what are you doing? ...
啊啊啊啊 你在干什么
Thank you.
多谢啦
They are coming.
他们要来了
You two'd better hurry.
你们俩最好快点
You don't got to tell me twice.
你没必要说两遍
Ed! Hurry!
埃德 快点呀
All right!
好
But before I go,
但走之前
I just want to tell you,
我想告诉你
you are the prettiest, nicest psychopath I've ever met.
你是我见过的最漂亮最善良的精神病人
You are so sweet.
你真好
Get off from me.
快从我身上滚下来
Get up.
起来呀
That way,
走那边
come on.
快点跟上
That way!
在那条路上
Lollipop for you,
棒棒糖给你
vanilla pop for you,
香草味的给你
and an ice cream sandwich.
还有一个冰淇淋三明治
Chocolate cup and another 20...
巧克力杯还有20个
Hey! What are you doing?
嘿 你们在干什么
Stealing your truck!
偷你的货车
Yeah! We are bringing it back!
没错 我们会还回来的
Come on.
开快点
Ah~ Ice cream tune.
啊 冰淇淋之歌
You turn that off!
你赶紧把那个关了
Oh, sorry, no ice cream for today.
噢 抱歉 今天不卖冰淇淋了
Got to go. Got to get back to good burgers.
我们得走了 得回到美味汉堡
Good burger is about to open.
美味汉堡马上就要开门营业了
We are gonna get there make sure nobody eat that poisoned sauce.
我们得快点赶到那 不能让任何人吃到有毒的酱料
Ice cream, folks! Look !
各位 好多冰淇淋呀 看
I got funky pops,
我拿了好看的棒棒糖
monster sickles and lemon juice pop.
怪物状的还有柠檬口味的
Ed! There is no time for frozen treat. Alright?
埃德 现在没时间说这些事 好吗
Wait! Give me one.
等下 给我一个冰淇淋
- There you go.   - Thanks!
-给你   -谢谢
What was that?
那是什么
I think it's a funk sickle.
我觉得它是一个镰刀状的冰淇淋棒棒糖
Get out of here.
死开
Have some vanilla.
来点香草味的吧
Take that up. A little bit of that.
来点这个吧 再换个口味
Have some raspberry's sundae.
来点覆盆子圣代
How do you like me now?
现在是不是对我感激涕零了
I am a dude firing ice cream.
我可是在发射冰淇淋炮弹的人
Get vanilla!
来点香草味的
Take some chocolate!
给你们点巧克力味的
Fight!
兄弟们 打起来
They will have you on this old hommie
把你放在这个上面
Nice spot, Wead.
好位置 韦德
Can't see. I can't see.
看不见了 我完全看不见了
stop!
停下
Look out ! look out!
当心 当心
Oh! No!
噢 不要
Wooohooo lost them!
哇噢噢噢噢 终于甩掉他们了
Hi! Welcome to good burger,
嗨 欢迎来美味汉堡店
home of the good burger. Can I take your order?
美味汉堡之家 你需要点什么
I'll have a good burger with extra sauce.
我要一个多加酱料的美味汉堡
Awww... haven't I told you I like it too?
啊啊啊 我有没有跟你说过我也喜欢这里的酱料
I will have the same thing.
我跟她点一样的
Derek, Step on it.
德雷克 加大油门
Here is your order. Two good burger, extra sauce
这是你们点的两个多加酱料的汉堡
Thank you.
谢谢
Oh pooo... I wanted mustard.
噢 不 我想要加点芥末
Hey! Hurry! Don't let anyone eat a good buger.
快点 别让任何人吃了有毒的汉堡
Come on Otis.
快点 欧迪斯
Noooooo
不 不 不 不
Get your hands off me
快点拿开你的手
What's going on? What's the...
发生什么事了 怎么了
Ed! Ed! What are you doing?
埃德 埃德 你在干什么
Ed, get off. Ge off the lady.
松手 放开那位女士
Ed, are you okey?
埃德 你还好吗
What happened?
发生什么事了
I just tackled some old lady
我刚刚成功阻止了一位老妇人吃汉堡
Alright ed!
太棒了 埃德
Excuse me! Would any of you mind
打扰一下 你们谁来告诉我
telling me why this is a good thing?
为什么这会是一件好事
This is why! Mondo burger poisoned our sauce.
这就是原因 蒙多汉堡在我们的酱料里投毒了
How could mondo buger poisoned our sauce?
但是蒙多汉堡是怎么在我们的酱料里投毒的呀
We'll explain that to you later.
等会再跟你解释
Right now just keep everyone from eating that sauce
现在就不要让任何人吃到有毒的酱料
and call the cops. Come on ed.
然后打电话给警察 跟我来 埃德
Where are we going?
我们去哪里
To get a can of thrampathol!
去拿一罐膨胀剂
What for?
拿那个干嘛
- Proof.   - Okay.
-当证据   -好
I need a hot gekush...
我需要一个热的...
Shall I ring?
我应该按铃吗
No. We are not gonna walk up in
不要 我们不是去邻居家
and ring the bell and say hi to the neighbor.
按门铃走进去然后说嗨
We are gonna find a way into the kitchen somehow.
我们得想办法找到一条通往厨房的路
I got an idea.
我有办法了
Follow me!
跟我来
Where are you going?
你要去哪里呀
Oh dear, careful!
天呀 小心点
Maybe you should... I don't know if...
也许你应该 我不知道
do you have a rope?
你有绳子吗
Come on it's easy
来吧 这很容易的
Yeah! Easy for you!
是呀 对你来说很简单
I don't even know the... Truck...
我甚至都不知道 货车
All right. Jump on to the pipe.
好 现在跳到那根管子上
Oh!
噢噢噢
See!
看
I just want...
我只想...
All right. You got it.
太好了 你做到了
Got What?
做到什么了
I'm swinging up from the dame pipe.
我在这根该死的管子上晃着呢
Oh, mama.
噢 妈妈
Ed!
埃德
埃德 埃德
Over here! Over here, come on.
这里 我在这里 快来
What are you doing in the straw?
你在那根管子里面做什么
Oh, it's right over the kitchen.
这根管子通往厨房
I can see it. Come on.
我可以看到厨房了 你快来吧
How do you expect me to get up there?
我怎么上到你那里去
Oh, it's easy. You just jump onto the burger,
很简单呀 你只要跳到那个汉堡上
jump on the fry, and up to the cup
再跳到薯条上 然后爬到杯子上
and see me at the straw.
然后你就可以跟我一起站在管子上了
What is it, man? The marking gladiator?
什么呀 你以为我是古罗马的勇士吗
Come on!
快点来吧
All right.
好吧
Can't believe
简直不敢相信
I'm climbing on the straw.
我居然在爬一根管子
Wow! The burger looks so small from up here.
哇 从这里看 汉堡店好小呀
Ed! Ed!
埃德 埃德
Ed! Are you in there?
埃德 你在里面吗
Here! Take my hand.
我在这里 抓住我的手
Ed! Ed!
埃德 埃德
Weee! Again! Again!
再来 再来
That was cool.
好好玩
Listen! Listen! I am going into that kitchen and I want you to count to ten
听好 我要去厨房了 你数到十
and came in to get the can of that chemical and get back to good burger, all right?
然后进厨房拿一罐膨胀剂 再返回美味汉堡 可以吗
All right.
可以
Ok.
好
One.
一
Two,
二
three...
三
Hey, everybody!
嗨 大家好
What happened?
看看发生什么了
How do you get here?
你怎么进来的
Wow. Look at this fancy kitchen!
哇 看看这个高档厨房
You know mama never have one of these when the electronic,
但妈妈做饭的时候
we always have a turning on...
从来都不会放这个
Let's catch him.
抓住他
If I were you,
如果我是你
I won't come any closer.
我就不会再靠近一步了
Get him!
抓住他
Oh!
噢
Get him!
一定要抓住他
Come on!
来呀
We'll get you. Go! Go! Let's go!
我们一定会抓住你的 走 快点走
Hehe.
嘿嘿
Go! Get him on the way!
快走 他在那边
All right,"punk"!
好啦 傻瓜
The game is over.
游戏结束了
Yeah! Your game is over
是呀 你快要玩完了
because right now my man Ed is on his way now to the police station
因为现在我的好兄弟埃德正拿着你们非法的膨胀剂
with a can of your illegal thrampathol...
去警察局报警呢
Hey! Dex! Got it!
嘿 德克斯 我拿到了
Get it!
赶紧拿走
Give me that.
把那个给我
Oh!
噢
Nice try, dude.
做得不错呀 两位
But you mess with Curt and going to the grinder.
但是你们别想在我这捣乱
Here you go, boss.
给你 老板
Thanks, Homes.
多谢 霍梅斯
This can is empty.
这个里面是空的
Haha.
哈哈哈
What an idiot!
真是个傻瓜
He stole an empty can!
他偷了一个空罐子
Ed! You stole an empty can!
埃德 你居然偷了一个空罐子
It wasn't empty when I found it.
当我发现它的时候 它可不是空的
Oh!
啊
噢
What's going on?
怎么回事儿
I don't know!
我不知道
The kitchen! Come on. Go!
厨房出事了 快去看看
Come on, Ed! Let's go!
埃德 我们快走
Grill! We've got to stop the grill!
是烤箱出了问题 我们得关了烤箱
Let's get out of here!
我们赶紧逃离这里
Yeah!
耶
Bang, bang!
梆 梆
Must be a shift change.
肯定是交接班时间咯 这么多人
Ah?
啊
Ah!!!!
Haha!!! Oh!
不要呀
Why?
为什么
Why!
Why have I got this?
为什么总是我
What are you? What are you put up on me?
你是谁 你打算怎么干
Sir. It's gonna be ok. You told our police to tie up.
先生 没事的 是你告诉我们要绑紧的
You don't understand,
你不明白
none of this is my fault, OK?
这都不是我的错 好吗
I don't know.
我不知道
Hey! Let's go out for some help.
嘿 我们去帮帮他们吧
I'll explain everything.
我会把所有事情解释清楚的
All is just a big misunderstanding.
这一切都是个误会
You don't understand. I don't know what happened.
你不明白的 我也不知道发生了什么
Oh, sure you do.
你当然知道了
Why don't you go ahead and tell your little police friend
为什么你不告诉你的警察朋友
that you make your piffy burger.
你是如何做出你们的超大汉堡的呢
All burger by using illegal food additive.
所有的汉堡里都有违法的食品添加剂
Is that true?
他说的是真的吗
No, he is lying. You are lying.
不 他在骗人 你在骗人
Full of crap.
全是瞎编的
Why don't we check this out
我们为什么不检查下这玩意儿
and we'll see who is lying.
然后看看是谁在说谎呢
You'd better come with us.
你最好跟我们一起来
Man, you are out of your mind.
你们疯了
You are crazy, man. You know who I am?
你们是不是疯了 知道我是谁吗
I don't mind.
我不在乎
Byebye.
拜拜
Remember,if you mess with good burger.
记好啦 如果你找美味汉堡的麻烦
You go into grinder.
你就死定了
You enjoy prison, man.
好好享受监狱时光吧
Curt got jail, Curt got jail, curt got jail, jail, jail.
科特进监狱了 科特进监狱了
进监狱了 进监狱了
Excuse me for a second.
等我一会儿
Mr. Wee.
韦老师
I can fix it. I can fix it.
我能搞定的
I can fix it.
我能修好
I don't have that time, but I have a couple of words for you.
我没那个时间等你 但我有话想对你说
Look,
呐
here is about half of the money I owe you for your car.
这个是我欠你的修车费的一半
And I guess I will have all of them by the end of summer.
在暑假结束之前我应该能还清你的钱
Enjoy your car. Bye bye, man.
好好享受你的豪车 再见咯
Somebody! Help me off. Just help me get the burger off.
谁能帮帮我 帮我把这个大汉堡推开
Come on, Ed,
来 埃德
so you pulled all the stuff meat in.
你把所有的膨胀剂都倒到肉里去了吗
Ah, I had to.
我不得不这么做呀
You had to?
不得不吗
Sure, I knew if I took the can,
当然呀 我知道如果我拿了罐子
there was a good chance I got caught.
我就很有可能被抓走
Then I thought
然后我想
if I did take the thrampathol to proper authorities,
如果我把膨胀剂拿到机构去验证
Curt will hire some high power attorneys
科特可能会雇佣一些有权威的律师
who will dispute all charges against him or Mondo burger
操控法律系统
by manipulating the legal system.
为他或者蒙多汉堡开罪
The way that American court system is congested these days.
而且美国法院最近都忙得要死
It will take the must convict of anything.
拖得太久会把罪证都抹去
So I thought,
然后我就想
I will take the matters on my own hand.
我要自己的方式来解决这件事
Just pull the thrampathol into the meat supply.
把所有的膨胀剂都倒到肉里
And let Mondo burger be a victim of its own foul play.
然后让蒙多汉堡自作自受
Wait, wait, wait,
等等 等等
you thought all of that?
这些都是你自己想出来的吗
Oh, sure. I'm not stupid.
当然 我又不蠢
Look, Ed.
埃德
About this contract, man.
关于这个合同
What do you say that we just forget it.
我们还是作废吧
You don't want to be partners?
你不想成为我的同伙了吗
Well, No, see.
不 只是
Is it because I'm black?
是因为我是黑人吗
No, it's not because you. Cause I'm...
不 不是因为 是因为我
look, forget it. We can be partners,
别管了 我们还是好伙伴
but the money is yours, all right? All of it.
但是钱都是你的
So, we are still buddies?
所以 我们还是好兄弟吗
Oh, you know it.
这不废话嘛
Haha, cool.
哈哈 太好了
Dexter.
德克斯特
I just want to say that,
我只想说
I'm really gonna miss you.
我会很想念你的
a lot.
很想很想
And Um.
呃
I will always remember you, Dextery.
我会一直记得你 德克斯特
In my thoughts and in my heart.
在我的脑海里 在我的心里
Good bye, my friend.
再见 我的朋友
Ed!
埃德
Ed! I'm not going anywhere, man.
埃德 我没打算离开这呀
Oh!
噢
Here comes the heros!
英雄们来了
Let's celebrate for the man who saved good burger, huh!
让我们一起来位这个拯救了美味汉堡的人欢呼
- Ed!   - Why?
-埃德   -干嘛
Come on! Ed! Come on! Ed!
英雄 埃德 英雄 埃德
Come on, Ed. Say something!
埃德 说点什么吧
Well. I guess there is only one thing left to say!
唯一要说的只有一句话
Welcome to good burger.
欢迎来到美味汉堡
Home of the good burger. Can I take your order?
这里是美味汉堡之家 你需要点什么
欢迎扫描搜索关注
树屋微信公众号：树屋字幕组
更多经典影视敬请登录树屋论坛：
http://treehousesub.com 查看下载~